pin1111.com 2014-06-29

# About Pinnacle Sports | About Us | How to Find Out More About Pinnacle Sports

#### Last updated on: Thurs, 21/01/2013 - 9:25 PDT

#### Pinnacle Sports collects information from our Internet clients at several different points on our Web site. We use this information to improve and maintain our Web site, and to provide our clients with the highest level of service available.

#### Your privacy is of the utmost importance to Pinnacle Sports. We feel that you have a right to know what information we collect, and how we use it. This statement discloses:

## What information do we gather from our Web site?

Pinnacle Sports collects two types of information when you visit our Web site:

Tracking, or aggregate, data that does not identify you personally, and is automatically collected from every visitor; this includes:

  * The time and date of your visit;
  * The specific pages which you visit;
  * The make and version of the Web browser you are using;
  * The brand and version of your computer's operating system;
  * The "Referrer" (the Web site and page from which you clicked to get to the Pinnacle Sports site);
  * The IP address of the computer you are using.

Information that identifies you personally, and is collected only if you register as a client of Pinnacle Sports; this includes:

  * Your name;
  * Your age;
  * Your postal address;
  * Your email address.

Close Panel 

## How we use the information

We use the tracking data to gather general demographic information, measure usage patterns, and gauge user trends. This allows us to better understand our visitors needs and tailor our content accordingly.

  * Pinnacle Sports uses IP addresses and page requests to track user movements and analyze user preferences. This gives us a broad view of where our visitors come from and what they are looking for on our Web site. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information and are kept separate from individual clients' records.

  * The information about your browser and operating system is used to verify that Pinnacle Sports’ Web server software is compatible with your computer’s configuration.

When a visitor registers as a client of Pinnacle Sports:

  * We require a postal address so that we can send payments by courier or standard mail. When making payments by bank transfer or credit card charge-back, we provide to the bank or credit card company the information necessary to send payment.

  * We require an email address to send our clients their unique username and password. We also use email to notify our clients of changes in service and, with the client's approval, to send promotional information.

  * We request the age of our clients in order to ensure that they are of age to legally place bets in our jurisdiction.

Close Panel 

## Who else has access to the information we collect?

Pinnacle Sports treats all of our clients' personal information as confidential, and will not disclose it or use it except as explained in this statement or as required by law.

Pinnacle Sports is the sole owner of the personal information we collect from our clients; we do not share it with any third party. We will not give, trade or sell this information to any organization or business, or to any individual not employed by Pinnacle Sports.

If a client provides personal information during an interaction with our customer service areas (for example, an email address or telephone number), we will use it only for the purpose of customer service. We will not sell a client's phone number to telemarketers or anyone else.

Pinnacle Sports is licensed and sanctioned by the Government of Curacao. Pinnacle Sports will not release information about our clients to any government.

Close Panel 

## What security measures are used to protect the integrity of your information?

The Pinnacle Sports Web site takes every precaution to protect our client's information. When clients submit sensitive information via the site, their information is protected both online and off-line.

When our registration form asks clients to enter sensitive information (such as credit card numbers), such information is encoded using SSL, the most powerful system available for Internet security and encryption. For information about SSL, visit this Web site: [http://support.microsoft.com/default.aspx?scid=kb;EN-US;q245152](http://support.microsoft.com/default.aspx?scid=kb;EN-US;q245152 "RSA Security website")

In addition to using SSL encryption to protect sensitive online transactions, we also do everything possible to protect our client's information off-line. All of our clients’ personal information, not just the sensitive information mentioned above, is restricted in our offices. Only those employees who need it to perform a specific job (for example, our customer service representatives) are granted access to personally identifiable information.

Finally, all computers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment. Pinnacle Sports uses the best available hardware and software technologies to block any unauthorized entry into our systems.

Close Panel 

## What choices are available to you regarding the collection and use of your information?

We provide certain options to allow our clients to customize their interface, including choice of language, betting format, and specific browser.

If you have any reason to believe that a breach of privacy may have occurred at Pinnacle Sports, or that any of the information held by Pinnacle sports about you is inappropriately handled, or if you have any questions, email our Customer Service Department at [csd@pinnaclesports.com](mailto:csd@pinnaclesports.com "Send e-mail to Customer Service Department") and we will investigate promptly.

Close Panel 

## How you can correct or change your information?

Clients of Pinnacle Sports have access to the data maintained about them. This includes a complete listing of recent bets: each wager placed; the wager amount; the day and time it was placed, and the outcome of the wager. Old records are periodically destroyed.

Clients may request that certain data be erased or amended. This may include changing personal details or settings; it does not include changing wagers. Pinnacle Sports will comply with all appropriate requests within a reasonable time.

A client may notify Pinnacle Sports of a change in mailing address, or to terminate their account.

The personal data associated with accounts that have been terminated are deactivated. Non-personal data may be converted into summary or aggregate statistics in which the personal identifiers are removed.

Close Panel 

## How and why we use cookies

Many Web users are concerned and possibly confused about the use of "cookies" on the Internet. A cookie is a small text file that is transferred from a web site to the hard drive of your computer. We use cookies to store a coded ID number, which identifies your browser to our server and allows us to track your activities while you visit Pinnacle Sports' Web site.

Since cookies are only text files, they cannot "run" on your computer and have no ability to search your computer for other information, or actively transmit data to anyone else. Since our cookie file is in a coded form, only Pinnacle Sports' Web server can read the cookie that it places on your hard drive. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites.

Pinnacle Sports' Web site uses cookies and URL tracking codes to measure the effectiveness of our advertising and our Web site, not to monitor the activities of individual customers. Pinnacle Sports does not disclose to advertisers any information about individual customers.

You can set your browser to automatically refuse all cookies or else to notify you any time a cookie is sent, so you can accept or reject it as you prefer. If you reject the cookie from Pinnacle Sports' Web site you can still use the site, but you may be limited in accessing or using certain areas.

For more information about cookies, go to these web sites:

  1. [http://wp.netscape.com/legal_notices/cookies.html](http://wp.netscape.com/legal_notices/cookies.html "Netscape Cookies Info")
  2. [http://www.microsoft.com/info/cookies.mspx](http://www.microsoft.com/info/cookies.mspx "Microsoft Cookies Info")

Close Panel 

## Links to other Web sites

The Pinnacle Sports Web site may contain links to other sites; we are not responsible for the practices of such other sites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Pinnacle Sports' Web site. We encourage our clients and visitors to be alert when they leave our site and to read the privacy statement of any Web site that collects personally identifiable information.

Close Panel 

## Where do we store your personal data?

The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area ("EEA"). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA, who work for us. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.

Close Panel 

## Notification of Changes

If Pinnacle Sports decides to change any parts of this privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Web site at least four weeks in advance of their taking effect. Our clients will always be made aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. Should any of our clients not agree to the changes, they will always have the option to close their account and to tell Pinnacle Sports to delete their personal information.

Close Panel 

## Related Articles

General Rules
